{
  "character_creation_questions": [
    {
      "question": "What kind of race do you want?",
      "answer": "I want a weird race!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What class are you interested in?",
      "answer": "I want a class that is not into magic at all"
    },
    {
      "question": "What background do you prefer?",
      "answer": "I want a background that involves being a hero"
    },
    {
      "question": "What alignment do you envision for your character?",
      "answer": "I want my character to be good and generous"
    },
    {
      "question": "What personality traits do you want your character to have?",
      "answer": "I want my character to be friendly, but cautious"
    },
    {
      "question": "What physical appearance do you imagine for your character?",
      "answer": "I want my character to be tall and in good shape, wide shoulders but with a friendly german like face"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of backstory do you have in mind?",
      "answer": "I want a backstory involving being the son of a dethroned dinasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are your character's goals or motivations?",
      "answer": "I want my character to seek undoing past wrongs"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of relationships does your character have?",
      "answer": "I want my character to have a loyal companion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What special abilities or skills do you want your character to possess?",
      "answer": "I want my character to be talented with his body but not the most intelectual, really strong and quick to think but objective and simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is your character's name?",
      "answer": "I want my character to be named Frugo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are your character's ability scores?",
      "answer": "I want high strenght and carisma"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of weapon do you prefer?",
      "answer": "I want big weapons : )"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a personal flaw of your character?",
      "answer": "My character is sometimes too simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does your character have any strong bonds with others?",
      "answer": "My character has a group of friends, the party members, a cleric, a paladin, a rogue and a bard"
    }
  ]
}